MUSIC
When I opened my eyes like god appearing before me,
She appeared before my eyes.
Like caught in a heavy downpour without an umbrella,
You drenched me in the rain of love.
Till I met you, All my days were listless.
After meeting her all days have become festivals.
I’ve got involved in a beautiful accident.
Though there were ways to escape, I willingly gave it up.
Oho..hoo…oho..hoo..ooh…o
ho..ooo..ooo..whoo..whoo
Whistle:...
Music...
I don’t know your name. I don’t know your place.
A beautiful bird doesn’t need a name.
I’m looking at you without you realizing.
Can the moon know the image on the river water?
I’m carrying a life inside my life Is this what you call love?
The burden on my heart...,
Is it love for you?
When I opened my eyes as a god appearing before me,
She appeared before my eyes
Music...
If you step on the road,
even street lights will wink at you.
Even Sun will refuse to set.
if you bathe in the river, even fish will get the fever.
Rain will rush down to touch you.
Even if an earthquake comes..
It can’t break my strong heart.
When a flower struck me, it gave in easily.
When I opened my eyes as a god appearing before me,
She appeared in front of my eyes.
Like caught in a heavy rainstorm without an umbrella,
You’ve soaked me in the rain of love.
Ooh ..ooh..oooo..oooo..ooh…ohoo..ooh…ooh…ooo..ooo…hoo…oho